
history_questions = {
    1: {
        "question": "How many days in a week were there in ancient Roman times?    ", "answer": "8"
    },
    2: {
        "question": "How many U.S. presidents have been assassinated?    ",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    3: {
        "question": "In which country did the Easter Rising take place in 1916?    ",
        "answer": "Ireland"
    },
    4: {
        "question": "Who built the first car in America? (Need first and last name.)    ",
        "answer": "Henry Ford"
    },
    5: {
        "question": "What nation separated from the United Kingdom in 1921?    ",
        "answer": "Ireland"
    },
    6: {
        "question": "In which country was the largest known T-Rex skeleton found?    ",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    7: {
        "question": "The Aztec people sacrificed about how many people per year?    \na) 100 \tb) 250,000\nc) 500,000\td) 1,000    ",
        "answer": "b"
    },
    8: {
        "question": "What scandal forced U.S. President Richard Nixon to resign in 1974?    ",
        "answer": "Watergate"
    },
    9: {
        "question": "Where was Cleopatra's birthplace?    ",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    10: {
        "question": "The Protestant Reformation was started by whom?    ",
        "answer": "Martin Luther"
    }
}


music_questions = {
    1: {
        "question": "What famous music festival took place in 1969?    ",
        "answer": "Woodstock"
    },
    2: {
        "question": "Which singer is a godmother to Elton John's two sons?    ",
        "answer": "Lady Gaga"
    },
    3: {
        "question": "The Grateful Dead's highly-devoted fanbase is known as what?    ",
        "answer": "Deadheads"
    },
    4: {
        "question": "The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame is situated in what US State?    ",
        "answer": "Ohio"
    },
    5: {
        "question": "Which pop singer's real name is Robyn Fenty?    ",
        "answer": "Rihanna"
    },
    6: {
        "question": "Which pop star played 27 different instruments on their debut album “For You”?    ",
        "answer": "Prince"
    },
    7: {
        "question": "The Spice Girls released their debut album in 1996. What was the name of the album?    ",
        "answer": "Spice"
    },
    8: {
        "question": "Which American rapper originally went by the name Lesane Parish Crooks?    ",
        "answer": "Tupac"
    },
    9: {
        "question": "What does the Italian musical term adagio mean?    ",
        "answer": "slow"
    },
    10: {
        "question": "Who sang a duet with Ed Sheeran on the song “Perfect”?    ",
        "answer": "Beyonce"
    }
}


sports_questions = {
    1: {
        "question": "In 1972, this American Football team went undefeated for the whole season, even during the Super Bowl. What was the team?    ",
        "answer": "Miami Dolphins"
    },
    2: {
        "question": "In American Football, a touchdown is worth how many points?    ",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    3: {
        "question": "How many NBA championships did Michael Jordan win with the Chicago Bulls (enter number)?    ",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    4: {
        "question": "The term 'home run' was already previously used in a different sport before becoming a mainstay in baseball vocabulary. What was that sport?    ",
        "answer": "Cricket"
    },
    5: {
        "question": "What pitcher holds the record for most complete games in an MLB career?    ",
        "answer": "Cy Young"
    },
    6: {
        "question": "What year did female American tennis legend, Serena Williams, win her first major tennis championship?    ",
        "answer": "1999"
    },
    7: {
        "question": "TWhat is the term for a zero score in tennis?    ",
        "answer": "love"
    },
    8: {
        "question": "Who was the first golfer to reach one million dollars in career earnings on the PGA Tour?    ",
        "answer": "Arnold Palmer"
    },
    9: {
        "question": "Who was named PGA Tour Rookie of the Year in 1996?    ",
        "answer": "Tiger Woods"
    },
    10: {
        "question": "How old was Tiger Woods when he won the Masters (enter number?)    ",
        "answer": "21"
    }
}


general_questions = {
    1: {
        "question": "A pool ball set includes how many balls?    ",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    2: {
        "question": "Other than water, what is the most consumed beverage?    ",
        "answer": "tea"
    },
    3: {
        "question": "The Munich beer festival is held in which month?    ",
        "answer": "October"
    },
    4: {
        "question": "Which famous singer's documentary was released in 2020 and is titled Miss Americana?    ",
        "answer": "Taylor Swift"
    },
    5: {
        "question": "Who was everyone's first friend on the MySpace platform (first name only)?    ",
        "answer": "Tom"
    },
    6: {
        "question": "What year did Game of Thrones premiere on HBO?    ",
        "answer": "2011"
    },
    7: {
        "question": "What is the world's oldest and most widely consumed alcoholic drink?    ",
        "answer": "beer"
    },
    8: {
        "question": "What is the national animal of Canada?    ",
        "answer": "beaver"
    },
    9: {
        "question": "How many stars are on the European Union flag (enter number)?    ",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    10: {
        "question": "HWhat letter represents potassium in chemistry and a strikeout in baseball?    ",
        "answer": "K"
    }
}
